const questions = [
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "What is the largest canyon in the world?",
        Correct: "Grand Canyon, USA",
        Incorrect: ["Verdon Gorge, France", "King’s Canyon, Australia", "Fjaðrárgljúfur Canyon, Iceland"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "What is the largest active volcano in the world?",
        Correct: "Mouna Loa",
        Incorrect: ["Mount Etna", "Mount Vesuvius", "Mount Batur"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "When was the book “To Kill a Mockingbird” by Harper Lee published?",
        Correct: "1960",
        Incorrect: ["1950", "1970", "1980"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "In which museum can you find Leonardo Da Vinci’s Mona Lisa?",
        Correct: "Le Louvre",
        Incorrect: ["Uffizi Museum", "British Museum", "Metropolitan Museum of Art"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "Who was George W. Bush’ vice president?",
        Correct: "Dick Cheney",
        Incorrect: ["Joe Biden", "Kamala Harris", "Al Gore"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "If you are born on the 1st of January, which star sign are you?",
        Correct: "Capricorn",
        Incorrect: ["Scorpio", "Libra", "Aries"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "Which country does not share a border with Romania?",
        Correct: "Poland",
        Incorrect: ["Ukraine", "Hungary", "Bulgaria"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "What was Euclid?",
        Correct: "A mathematician",
        Incorrect: ["A philosopher", "A poet", "A painter"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "In which country is the baht the currency?",
        Correct: "Thailand",
        Incorrect: ["Vietnam", "Malaysia", "Indonesia"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "Which natural landmark is not in Australia?",
        Correct: "Moeraki Boulders",
        Incorrect: ["The Great Barrier Reef", "Uluru", "12 Apostles"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "How many players are in a cricket team?",
        Correct: "11",
        Incorrect: ["8", "9", "10"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "Which constellation is on the Australian flag?",
        Correct: "The southern cross",
        Incorrect: ["Orion", "Ursa Minor", "Scorpius"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "Which chemical element has Ag as a symbol?",
        Correct: "Silver",
        Incorrect: ["Gold", "Iron", "Carbon"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "How long is the border between the United States and Canada?",
        Correct: "5,525 miles",
        Incorrect: ["3,525 miles", "4,525 miles", "6,525 miles"]
    },
    {
        Number: "",
        Question: "Which French king was nicknamed the “Sun King”?",
        Correct: "Louis XIV",
        Incorrect: ["Francis I", "Louis XVI", "Charlemagne"]
    },
];

export default questions;